I'm at the WGT, the Wave Gothic Treffen, the biggest, best known gothic festival in Germany and worldwide.
And this is the agra area where most of the festival happens, the main stages, the campground, the shopping hall.
And I'm going to take you along with me today throughout the whole city.
There are more than 30 event locations, there are concerts, there are plays, museums which you can go to.
So there's really a lot to see and there are so many people.
It's a perfect place to meet up, to see new bands and just enjoy a beautiful weekend here,
dress up and have a great time.
And then I won't leave you alone anymore
I'm here at the merch area.
It's bright and early, just before 1 o'clock.
A lot of people are still asleep at the campground or their hotels.
For me, it's easier to record this video when it's empty.
So we're going now.
Let's go.
You can see her
Whenever it rains
From Rome to New Orleans
Passing all the graves
I just found this and I think it's really cool because it's not scale mail, not metal,
but patent leather which makes it really light and it's also nice and shiny and something
different.
It's really nice.
I'm dying
Just like a gothic girl
Lost in the darkened world
My little gothic gloom
I'm starting to lie
Eraser cuts for you, baby
You can see she's
On her road to ruin
Stigmata from crucifixion
On her pale white skin
Try for pagan art
She loves her tattoo
In the gypsy mark
We're doing a fitting now because I am walking in a fashion show for Instinct Berlin soon.
So trying this one on and see how it looks and also maybe something else.
I just love her design, it's so cool.
And this kind of futuristic harness with this ski is really nice.
So this is the prototype she just put on me to see how it looks because she just did that.
And this is the first fitting for this piece.
I can't wait to see it on the shelf when she's done the regular second version of it.
We'll see you next time.
We'll be right back.
Very special outfit today.
I bought these shoes on sale and thought, well, I need the rest of the outfit for that,
so I decided on a white PVC catsuit.
And I have to be really careful today not to wear anything or touch anything to get
the white pvc strained immediately not a great festival offer but i thought hey let's do
something different in this black mass of people it's raining and i found a foxy hey
we're at the heighten store of the renaissance fair here
and um wanted to see some bands but now it's pouring cats and dogs
so luckily she hasn't has an umbrella because i don't i'm prepared you're prepared i don't i'm not
Somebody
I fell in love with my killer
This is high-tech emotion
Flowing kisses with a machine gun
In the pain of the emotion
And you've been good in your prison
How long is that going to last?
Out in the critical distance
I can't...
Last stop for today before I'm going to see more concerts is the Heidnische Storf, the Renaissance Fee here.
It's actually one of two medieval markets in Leipzig during the Meaghertie
and this one is closer to the campground so I prefer this one also because it's bigger
and it's just really cool to just chill here on the Monday and Sunday, sit down on the
grass, have a drink, just walk around, eat something, go shopping and meet your friends.
Somebody, somebody, somebody, somebody.
Thank you.